{
    "subject": "resource/Karl_Weierstrass",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Mathias_Lerch",
    "human_readable": "Karl Weierstrass was a doctoral student of Mathias Lerch.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9786457419395447,
            "question": "Did Karl Weierstrass receive his doctorate from Mathias Lerch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.855353057384491,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Karl Weierstrass and Mathias Lerch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.814326286315918,
            "question": "Who was Karl Weierstrass's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8082776069641113,
            "question": "What can we infer about the influence of Mathias Lerch on Karl Weierstrass's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6747598648071289,
            "question": "Was Mathias Lerch a professor at a university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6068999171257019,
            "question": "Were there other notable students under Mathias Lerch's guidance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5351739525794983,
            "question": "Who served as Karl Weierstrass's mentor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5301111936569214,
            "question": "What field of study did Karl Weierstrass likely pursue based on this information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44074746966362,
            "question": "Are there any famous works or discoveries associated with Mathias Lerch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18590973317623138,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the academic relationship between these two mathematicians?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Weierstrass was a doctoral student of Mathias Lerch.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7692_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous works or discoveries associated with Mathias Lerch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7692_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study did Karl Weierstrass likely pursue based on this information?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7692_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who served as Karl Weierstrass's mentor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7692_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7692_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided documents state that Matthias Lerch studied under Karl Weierstrass, not the other way around. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention in the documents of Karl Weierstrass being a doctoral student of Mathias Lerch. In fact, one document mentions Mathias Lerch studying under Karl Weierstrass and Leopold Kronecker at the University of Berlin, but it does not suggest a reversal of roles with Karl Weierstrass being a doctoral student of Lerch."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information suggesting that Karl Weierstrass was a doctoral student of Mathias Lerch. In fact, the documents indicate that Mathias Lerch attended courses taught by Karl Weierstrass and others at the University of Berlin during his studies."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Karl Weierstrass was not a doctoral student of Mathias Lerch. Instead, Mathias Lerch studied under Karl Weierstrass at the University of Berlin during 1884-85.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several texts state that Lerch was a student of Weierstrass, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Mathias Lerch was actually a student of Karl Weierstrass, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Karl Weierstrass was a professor of mathematics and not a doctoral student. He taught at the K\u00f6nigliches Gewerbeinstitut, which later became the Technische Universit\u00e4t Berlin, and had students like Adolf Hurwitz and Vojt\u011bch Jarn\u00edk, among others.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}